As of this morning, you can see
that I made over 421,000 US dollars in
just over six months without taking one
single sales call.
I, by accident, created a sales system,
which means that I can make sales at the
touch of a button and save the time
that most people spend on the phone doing
other
productive things, like this video.
There are a few main problems
that I see with taking sales calls in
2024, so let's
quickly look into them.
Problem number one, when people say no,
or they say they
need more time, or need to think about it,
or whatever reason they don't purchase
your services,
you've now wasted a pretty intense period
of time, which could've
been used doing something so much better.
There are literally 10X things
that you could do instead,
which I'll get onto in
a second. Two, people that
are ready to buy, and those of which
that are A-plus
grade clients,
don't particularly like taking sales
calls.
Right next to me, I have my dog, Alfie,
and he's crazy.
He's a breed of dog in Australia called a
Kelpie, and we had this problem that
every time a bike went past with a dog,
he was losing his shit. Pain point.
So I come home, look at my missus, I go,
"We need a dog trainer." I tried looking
around on Google a little bit. Instead,
I went to someone that I knew would have a
good dog training knowledge in the area.
They recommended someone to me,
so I reach out.
When I reached out to this person,
he sent me a list of all of his prices on
a neat
PDF, and he said, "Let me know
which you would like,
and we can start." I looked
through it. First thing I thought was,
"Oh my God, this guy is expensive," which
immediately made me think he was good.
And second of all,
I looked through his packages,
found one that I thought would be
perfect for us, said,
"I'd like to do this package." He goes,
"Cool.
Send the payment,
and we'll pick a date." That's exactly how
it worked, and he was
great. However, in this process, if
that dog trainer had said,
"Hey, mate.
Why don't we jump on a phone call
together, and we can
discover what would be the right option
for you moving forward, and we can talk
pricing on the phone?" I would've run a
mile.
One, I don't want to take a phone call.
I don't want to chat to some random dog
trainer.
I want to know what it is you offer,
how much it's going to cost me,
and I want to
get a general idea of whether
or not you're good or not.
I got those things from the PDF
that he sent me, therefore,
I'm not wasting
his time, and he's not wasting mine